(Sheldon:)Good golly, it's as if
it's actually happening to me.
(Priya(at door):)Raj finally went to bed.
(Leonard:)Sheldon's still up.
(Priya:)You said he goes
to bed at 9:00.
(Leonard:)Yeah, he does, but he got caught
up in a computer game and...
Hit troll with axe!
(Sheldon:)My, this is one tough troll.
(Priya:)Can't you get rid of him?
(Leonard:)If the past is any
indication, no.
(Sheldon:)Leonard, I'm trapped
in quicksand!
The axe is dragging me down!
Drop axe!
Drop axe, brilliant!
(Leonard:)Give me a minute.
(Priya:)Sheldon.
(Sheldon:)Hold on.
Trying to figure out
(Sheldon:)how to get the bucket,
(Sheldon:)so I can carry the mud
past the dragon.
(Leonard:)Sheldon, you need to
work in the morning.
I know!
Well, then bed, mister!
Five more minutes!